[ED].
Best regards.
I think we are still on stage today, but before we do that, let me recommend you.
Thank you very much.
I'm very happy.
Please have them eat it.
Is that OK?
Thank you very much.
I'm going to have a whole melon cream soda.
What should I do?
Surely there will be a lucky best speaking of
Ibaraki is the best producer of melons.
Melons are also the largest producer?
That's right!
That's great!
I'll definitely drink it when I come here.
I don't know.
It's delicious.
The melon flavor and the sweetness of the vanilla ice cream
It's so good!
I'm sure of it.
Whole melon!
Luxurious!
It's hot.
Because it's summer.
The sizzle of the soda and the sweetness of the ice cream.
And it's going to dry out.
This kin melon is the best thing ever.
I can't even taste a sip right now.I haven't even taken a sip now and I can't taste it.
I'm gonna go brush it off.
Isn't it amazing? It's so authentic!
Oh, my God!
What kind of ramen is this?
This is shio ramen.
Wow!
I'll take it from the soup!
Delicious!
It's a great way to get some salt in the summer heat.
How are the noodles?
I'm gonna make them wait.
That's great.
What do you think?
Looks so good!
Looks great.
That's bold.
You're going all out.
Feels good.
How is it?
It's so authentic! I love that we can sell such authentic ramen for a fraction of the price!
The ingredients are seriously gorgeous!
So many!
Even the bamboo shoots are huge!
Delicious! I can't get enough!
Looks so good!
Tsukuba Chicken, right?
Yes, it is.
Delicious!
I'm an Ibaraki girl.I'm an Ibaraki woman.
Yes, I'm a local woman.
Bon appétit.
Hmm? The blue clock changed?
Did the blue clock go? Just now.
That was quick.
It's so good! It's so crispy.
It's delicious.
It's got a little bit of sour sauce.
It's so good!
It's a perfect match with the Tsukuba Soy Sauce.
Delicious!
It's great!
This kind of rice makes me want to eat more!
It's the same with ramen.
Gattun!
Too juicy!
It's so good!
I'm definitely going.
It's great!
I'll go for it, then.
Snow crab croquettes!
Amazing!
Nice size.
Looks delicious.
Bon appétit!
It's popular to eat it with one hand at Kos.
Indeed.
It's so delicious and look at it. I'm sorry.
I'll show you the cross section I ate.I'll show you the cross section I ate.
Wow!
The crab is all over the place.
It looks super delicious.
Isn't it amazing?
It's 80% crab.
I could really taste the crab flavor.
It's amazing that it's a separate meal.
It's delicious.
It's more than crab, but it's so much more than crab.
It's crab no matter how far you go.
I can't eat it in terms of crab.
This crab cream croquette,
It's the best cream croquette in Japan.
It's amazing.
It's like larva.
No matter how far you go, it's still crab.
It's really delicious.
Looks delicious.
The fried rice cake looks a little bit sweet potato.
But it's not so sweet potato-like.
It's like you can eat it without any crunchiness.
It's good.
It's delicious. Very good.
Thank you very much.
And now, the last one.
Thank you for watching until the end.
I've never done a food report before, but I'm a new member, and this is my first commemorative report.
I'm a new member, but this is my first time to do a food report, so I'm going to have some leftover seafood.
Let's eat!well
hmm.
diese a now law
I don't know if you've ever been to a part-timber farm, but you know what I'm talking about...
thoo
Hey, you're not catching on!
Hey, you're cute.
Delicious, isn't it?
It looks so good! It smells so good!
It's so good.
I love it. Hand-pulled yakisoba noodles.
I know you're all going on stage now.
Could you say a few words to the fans?
It's really hot today.
I'd like to have a lot of fun with all of you who are participating in the Lucky Fest.
I'm looking forward to having a great time with all of you at Lucky Fest!
I'd like to thank all the artists who provided songs for EBITCHU, and I'm looking forward to seeing you all at the festival.
I'm so happy to see so many artists on the same day!
I know so many people.
I feel like I'm meeting all my relatives.
We are going to sing the songs that you have given us.
I hope we will be able to share our summer memories with you all!
I will eat a lot and do my best!